<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jonathan&#39;s Sports Blog</title>
    <link>http://jonathanzettlerblog.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jonathan&#39;s Sports Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jonathanzettlerblog.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who Was The Lakers Best Shooter Off The Bench This Season</title>
      <link>http://jonathanzettlerblog.github.io/2022/04/26/who-was-the-lakers-best-shooter-off-the-bench-this-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jonathanzettlerblog.github.io/2022/04/26/who-was-the-lakers-best-shooter-off-the-bench-this-season/</guid>
      <description>The Los Angeles Lakers had a very disappointing 2021-2022 season after acquiring many new names during the off-season. It is expected that the Lakers will look to move many of their players during this off-season, but there are still some players who had good seasons despite the rough season. My objective here is to look at the Lakers best shooters off the bench to see who might be a bright idea to resign for next season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://jonathanzettlerblog.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jonathanzettlerblog.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jonathan Zettler. I am senior at the University of Nebraska- Lincoln who is majoring in Sports Media and Communications and I will be posting visualizations here that I produce from breaking down the data from sports like football, basketball, and volleyball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Nebraska Basketball&#39;s Defense Improve Throughout the 2021-2022 Season</title>
      <link>http://jonathanzettlerblog.github.io/2022/03/31/did-nebraska-basketball-s-defense-improve-throughout-the-2021-2022-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jonathanzettlerblog.github.io/2022/03/31/did-nebraska-basketball-s-defense-improve-throughout-the-2021-2022-season/</guid>
      <description>It’s no secret that Nebraska had a rough basketball season this year going 10-22 overall and 4-16 in the Big Ten. The team continued to drop games because of poor defense, but did the Cornhuskers defense improve at all throughout the season?
Defense clearly was a struggle for the team as many fans pointed out that opposing teams would have their best shooting nights against the Cornhuskers. Did Nebraska’s opponents really shoot that well against them?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
